<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bored Game</string>

    <!--Building Text-->
    <string name="lumber_mill_name">Lumber mill</string>
    <string name="lumber_mill_description">A run-of-the-mill lumber mill. The lumber mill helps produce more lumber for your town. A counter is added for every wood resource card you draft. Remove %s counters to gain 1 wood.</string>

    <string name="smeltery_name">Smeltery</string>
    <string name="smeltery_description">Great for smelting. The smeltery helps produce more iron for your town. A counter is added for every iron resource card you draft. Remove %s counters to gain 1 iron.</string>

    <string name="mason_name">Mason</string>
    <string name="mason_description">The Mason is where villagers go to rock. The Mason helps produce more stone for your town. A counter is added for every stone resource card you draft. Remove %s counters to gain 1 stone.</string>

    <string name="jeweler_name">Jeweler</string>
    <string name="jeweler_description">Not all that glitters is gold, but everything here is gold. The jeweler helps produce more gold for your town. A counter is added for every gold resource card you draft. Remove %s counters to gain 1 gold</string>

    <string name="mana_well_name">Mana well</string>
    <string name="mana_well_description">A magical well. The mana well helps produce more mana for your town. A counter is added for every mana resource card you draft. Remove %s counters to gain 1 mana.</string>

    <string name="mercenary_guild_name">Mercenary Guild</string>
    <string name="mercenary_guild_description">A vile breeding ground for despicable sellswords looking to make a quick buck, a perfect place to hire some fodder for your army. Hire a mercenary for 1 iron and 4 gold.</string>

    <string name ="summoners_guild_name">Summoners\' Guild</string>
    <string name ="summoners_guild_description">A congregation of powerful magic users. You can enlist their aid to summon golems at a cost. Summon a wood golem for 1 wood, 2 gold, and 3 mana</string>

    <!--Character Text-->
    <string name="human_class">Human</string>
    <string name="human_descript">Humans have been around the longest of all of the races that inhabit this world.
        Though they lack natural strengths, they are highly adaptable;
        It\'s their ingenuity that has afforded them to survive this long amongst such naturally stronger races. </string>

    <string name="navigation_open">Navigation Drawer opened</string>
    <string name="navigation_closed">Navigation Drawer closed</string>


    <!--Action Card Text-->
    <string-array name="action_card_names">
        <item>Ruined Shipment(Wood)</item>
        <item>Ruined Shipment(Iron)</item>
        <item>Ruined Shipment(Stone)</item>
        <item>Ruined Shipment(Gold)</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="action_card_descriptions">
        <item>Play during the draft resolve step. All players receive only 50% (Rounded down) of the wood they drafted this draft step.</item>
        <item>Play during the draft resolve step. All players receive only 50% (Rounded down) of the iron they drafted this draft step.</item>
        <item>Play during the draft resolve step. All players receive only 50% (Rounded down) of the stone they drafted this draft step.</item>
        <item>Play during the draft resolve step. All players receive only 50% (Rounded down) of the gold they drafted this draft step.</item>
    </string-array>
    <integer-array name="action_card_mana_costs">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>1</item>
    </integer-array>

</resources>
